The sky is grey, dusty and dull.
It makes it look like a completely new city.
I feel so lost.
As a little child, I never once cried in front of my mom.
I promised myself I would never cry in front of her.
After my father left us both, my mom cried the tears that should have been mine as well.
When she robbed me of my sadness, I felt something for the first time.
Something I couldn't name.
How could I know the thing I was never given?
How could I define it?
This comfortable world of being alone, it was all mine.
But then...
Hana!
You came and gave my world color again.
I'm glad that you're okay, Hana.
I've been looking for you.
You scared me.
I got a call from your mom saying that you disappeared.
Come on, let's go home now.
Hm?
Hana?
I suddenly became so embarrassed.
For trying to act so tough.
So why then?
You once offered me a safe space, remember?
So why are you abandoning me now?
Good morning, Sanai.
Sanai's hair is always so silky.
It even looks good when it's parted to the side.
Hana-bee, you're awake?
Good morning.
What's the matter?
Sanai.
you know what i get it
i already know everything really i'm not that stupid
but i know that if i told her there's no way she'd understand
she'd probably actually hate me seriously
do i really care if she hates me or not
there was a time when i really didn't know that answer
how could you say that
how could you say that about akane
huh you really don't know you're such a kid sometimes mugi
do you see now
but why he's so old i bet that guy's an old college professor
i cried myself to sleep that night
but by the next day
hi there sorry i'm late
akane showed up at my house to tutor me as usual
you want some cake i just got them
nice she's wearing the same clothes as yesterday
she's doing that because she looks cute at that angle
i bet
she can't live without a man giving her attention
and just like that
when i knew that's the way she thinks
akane suddenly became this fragile sympathetic girl to me
huh
mugi
you've got some icing on your face
i'm gonna be sick
that's the smell
of the love hotel shampoo
isn't it
wanna lick
huh
no
i'm good
okay then
this sick woman
she's a mess
but since then i can't help but
oh silly me
i dropped my pencil
did she calculate this
oh
i'm sorry
does she plan out everything she does around men
but i was useless
falling further into her trap
oh
so that's what you like
ouch
looking back
maybe she was just jealous
in her own way
i bet she'd be like
are you insane
there's no way
you're so pathetic
just die already
truthfully i don't hate how honest she can be
it's refreshing
huh
today's saturday
i've got nothing to do
but
why
i didn't think you'd actually come
huh
why not
please
i need you
to distract me for a while
i really hate wasting time
let's just do it
huh
oh i mean
i didn't just
that's exactly why you called me
it's fine
i'm partly to blame for that
hey
you know
i don't want you to feel like you have to do this
okay
you want sex right
well
well yeah
you know what
yeah
we've never done it when you've wanted me to do it before
so then
this makes us even
she went home afterwards
not bothering to spend the night
hey
hey there
muki
hey
morning
it's so hot
summer vacation is coming up real soon
you know we're in advanced courses right
apparently they're going to give us a ton of homework
at times it seems
muki and i were incredibly close
it wasn't just my imagination
but other times
we were practically strangers
we spent less time alone together
and we stopped talking about things that might get too real
i ended up not telling him about brother
and the whole confessing his feelings
we each got a sense
that the other had more things they were hiding from us knowing
we were even trying to avoid the trouble of asking about it
i wonder why
is sanai enough
to satisfy my need
i think so
if it's just about filling my loneliness
i don't really need muki anymore
no
not anymore
muki
did you sleep with someone else
you did too
didn't you
i did
i can tell
because
what
it's fine
we probably did it for the same reason
it's all because
it started to feel really good
it did
hey
how come
you know i hate to feel pain
but
it just
it just felt so good at the moment
me too
like i was saying
muki and i are so similar
like how terrible we both are
another day
another hour
time passes equally for everyone stuck here
so does that mean it's up to us
whether life is boring or not
the sound of the bell
the bell dictates timetables
when you arrive at school
when you leave school
after school
when you sleep
when you awake
time must be divided in order to be visible
i hate it
this place dictates so much
uh
excuse me
the number one thing i desire most in the world
is for something to break the mundane routine of everyday life
freedom
it's been a while since you last came over
uh
um
i know
it has
why are you so embarrassed
stupid
hey
i'm not
stupid
huh
hanabi
yeah
that's the look right there
you do that a lot
those eyes
she seems frightened
and confused
she still looks directly at me
she's so pretty
it makes me want to ruin her perfection
that's where my mind always goes
i know it's because i'm a man
and we're scum
it makes me feel disgusted
mugi
i want it
what did she say
not again
even i have things i want to keep closed off from the rest of the world
oh i'm sorry
i haven't given you my answer yet
have i
uh no
don't make me say it out loud
what a poor
will you
to be honest
yes
it's just
we still don't know each other all that well mr kanai
ah
today was a bust too
so then why don't we remedy that
that okay
just another boring day
hey mr kanai
do you happen to be free tonight
boring boring boring boring
this is all so unfortunate
i mean come on now
it's like could you try a bit harder you know
uh uh
are you meaning your students
no not them
i drank way too much because i was angry
this is just great
i certainly didn't plan on drinking this much tonight
oh well
it's his fault for being so boring honestly
are you really not going to drink anything
uh no i can't
alcohol
doesn't agree with me
oh jeez
i knew from the start that he would be boring
but he was even more boring than i thought
crap
i really hate being around such boring people
wait where are you going
you haven't given me an answer
you really want an answer
um
i mean that
would you
oh
are
are you okay
i'm relieved
hana
what
i didn't mean that
i just said it out of habit
why did this happen now
i take it all back
looks like this boring day
might have just gotten a lot more interesting
i'm feeling it now
is that a fading hickey
moogie
hey
stop it you idiot
how come
you don't want to show my kisses
are you hiding them from someone
not really
but in that case
i want you to go all the way today
hold on now
that's breaking our rules
we can't
there she goes again with her recklessness
that hysteric fickle and egocentric remark
i'm not equipped to deal with this
seriously
so it's a motel after all
no
let's see
oh yeah
that's right
i agreed to look at the skyline
because i felt sorry for him
this here
is my own
special little spot
and of course we just ended up here
are
are you sure
he wants permission
he's actually asking me at this point
honestly
what the hell do you see in him hana
say
that hana b from class c is very cute
don't you think
huh
you two seem like you are always so close at school
hana
she's just a good friend
that's all she is
she grew up near me
we're like brother and sister that's all
why
does it seem like i give her special treatment
oh
it's not that
maybe i'm being weird
feeling jealous about her like this
this is all too easy
stop
it hurts
i can't go through this
what
your body now feels
so cold
i don't want you getting cold
why do you think we can't do it mookie
well
what do you mean why
you don't really love me right
then i do love you
what do you mean by saying then
you want it that bad
something's wrong with you
hey
how about
my date for real
i'm leaving
Wait.
What?
Are you still a virgin?
I'm going home now.
I'm alone.
I hate being alone.
Being alone makes me feel so empty.
I want to sleep with someone so bad.
Honestly.
How weak have I become?
I'm nothing but a pathetic mess.
Hey, Mr. Kanai and I...
We had sex.
...
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-a-tta-ta-ta-ta-た a-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-t.
As you are Spanish.
I want to know how many itemsdrums are rebels forMeets today.
There will be various streams in the yearbook of his бр Yoga.
I want to know that the희 table is republic.
Then we'll find tier 26thículos on FR 9.
The keiner is cozies catch about.
Her team hasзVers very rumored at losing time
and also the result of hismelons in front of the city and of the Dol登録 Academy are going to say with us.